pheedo.com 2012-03-30

# Pheedo :: Privacy

## Privacy Policy

* * *

## What Personal Information About Customers Does Pheedo Collect?

  * **Information You Give Us:** Pheedo collects personal information when you register with Pheedo to use our products or services or when you enter into promotions or sweepstakes. Pheedo also collects information about your transactions with us. When you register or enter into a transaction we ask for information such as your name, email address, billing address, phone number, credit card information, and certain optional information. You may opt not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future services for you, and communicating with you.
  * **Automated Information:** We receive and store certain types of information automatically whenever you interact with us. For instance, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses www.pheedo.com. Pheedo automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie, and the page you request. Pheedo receives IP addresses from all users because this information is automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page.
  * **E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Pheedo if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers.
  * **Information from Other Sources:** Pheedo may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

### What About Cookies?

  * Cookies are small text files that your Web browser stores on your computer's hard drive. These text files only contain information you have already given to us and enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide personalized features within Pheedo's services and products.
  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Pheedo's features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

### How Does Pheedo Use The Information It Collects?

Pheedo uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, customer contact, notifying you of new services or products, research, and anonymous reporting.

### Does Pheedo Share the Information It Receives?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below and with subsidiaries Pheedo, Inc. controls that either are subject to this Privacy Policy or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy.

  * **Agents:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include sending e-mail and postal mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 
  * **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the event that Pheedo, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 
  * **Subscription to RSS Feeds via Email:** Pheedo provides services that enable users to receive updates of our advertiser and publisher partnersâ€™ RSS feeds via email. In order to provide this service Pheedo collects the email addresses of users. Pheedo may share the email addresses with the advertiser and/or publisher partnersâ€™ on whose behalf we deliver the RSS feed content. 
  * **Protection of Pheedo and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Pheedo, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 
  * **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

### What About Aggregate or Non-Personally Identifiable Information?

Pheedo aggregates (gathers up data across all user accounts) personal information and may disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing, promotional, or other business purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose any information that could be used to identify you personally. _For example, we may disclose to third parties information about how many people used our services in the last week, but we will not disclose who those people are._ Certain information, such as your name, email address, password, credit card number, and bank account number, are not disclosed to these third parties in a personally identifiable manner without your explicit consent.

### How Secure Is Information About Me?

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. 
  * Your Pheedo Account Information is password-protected. 
  * In certain areas, Pheedo uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

### Which Information Can I Access?

Pheedo gives you access to a range of information about your account and your interactions with Pheedo for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.

### What Choices Do I Have?

  * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such Pheedo features. 
  * You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the "Which Information Can I Access?" section above. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. 
  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you will not be able to use important Pheedo features if you do not use cookies. 
  * A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at Pheedo if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist. 
  * In addition, the Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own Web site, _[Site Seeing on the Internet](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.shtm)_. 

### Children

Pheedo does not provide its services to children under 13 years of age.

### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit Pheedo, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Service including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Oregon. If you have any concern about privacy at Pheedo, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Terms of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. 
  * We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Pheedo account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form or you can contact us at:

Pheedo Customer Care - Privacy Policy Issues 469 Ninth Street, Suite 210 Oakland, CA 94607

Version 9.9.09
